<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>

<channel rdf:about="http://slashgeo.org/">
<title>Slashgeo</title>
<link>http://slashgeo.org/</link>
<description>In+ersec+ion for Spatial People</description>
<dc:language>en-us</dc:language>
<dc:rights>Copyright &#169; 2007, Spatial Enlightenment</dc:rights>
<dc:date>2007-03-29T15:20:24+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:publisher>Slashgeo.org</dc:publisher>

<dc:creator>satri@slashgeo.org</dc:creator>
<dc:subject>News and discussions about GIS, Remote Sensing and everything Geospatial</dc:subject>
<syn:updatePeriod>hourly</syn:updatePeriod>
<syn:updateFrequency>1</syn:updateFrequency>
<syn:updateBase>1970-01-01T00:00+00:00</syn:updateBase>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1425203&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1419228&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1315235&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/218214&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/2055253&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/1424242&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/1417231&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/2023250&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/148259&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/1354248&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1624220&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1424258&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1417202&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1323228&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1316219&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/1435228&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/1423244&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/146219&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/2119234&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/143250&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/149239&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/1344213&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/2050218&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/1717216&amp;from=rss" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/1311251&amp;from=rss" />
 </rdf:Seq>

</items>
<image rdf:resource="http://slashgeo.org/images/topics/slashgeo.gif" />
<textinput rdf:resource="http://slashgeo.org/search.pl" />
</channel>

<image rdf:about="http://slashgeo.org/images/topics/slashgeo.gif">
<title>Slashgeo</title>
<url>http://slashgeo.org/images/topics/slashgeo.gif</url>
<link>http://slashgeo.org/</link>
</image>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1425203&amp;from=rss">
<title>InfoNow Migrating 20 Million Users to the Virtual Earth Platform</title>
<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1425203&amp;from=rss</link>

<description>The LM/VE blog informs us Microsoft just won over 20 million new users of Virtual Earth with the migration of Infonow. From the blog: "InfoNow supplies locator and analysis solutions to some of the best known brands in the world like Bank of America, Maytag, HP, Visa and many more. Their Locator applications run on the web, mobile phones and via voice, but that's just the start. For instance, their customers benefit from rich Content Management tools that enable them to get their location data geocoded and in the system. But perhaps most important is the business intelligence that can be gained from mining activity logs of the locator applications." The Microsoft press release can be found here.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-29T15:20:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>microsoft</dc:subject>
<georss:point>47.669 -122.124</georss:point>
<slash:department>someone-will-get-a-promotion-for-this-success</slash:department>
<slash:section>industry</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1419228&amp;from=rss">
<title>FOSS4G 2007 - Free and Open Source Software for Geospatial 2007</title>
<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1419228&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The FOSS4G 2007, the Free and Open Source Software for Geospatial 2007 conference, has been in preparation for some time already. This year, it will be held in Victoria (BC) Canada. Paul Ramsey announced the Workshops and Labs program are now established. This conference is increasingly important in the geospatial community. The call for presentations ends in late June. From the main site: "The annual Free and Open Source Software for Geospatial (FOSS4G) conference brings together the people who create, use, and support open spatial software. No other event brings together members of the open source development, open data creation, and open standards promotion communities like FOSS4G. Find out more about FOSS4G." See this entry on the future of GITA vs FOSS4G conferences. See also related stories below for FOSS4G 2006 items.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-29T14:39:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>new_event</dc:subject>
<georss:point>48.427919 -123.357368</georss:point>

<slash:department>brace-for-impact</slash:department>
<slash:section>industry</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1315235&amp;from=rss">
<title>3DConnexion SpaceNavigator Now Works with ArcMap 9.2 and NASA World Wind 1.4</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/29/1315235&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>Spatially Adjusted tells us there is now a 3DConnexion SpaceNavigator driver for ESRI ArcMap 9.2. Meanwhile, The Earth is Square tells us NASA World Wind 1.4 is officially supported. Is this newsworthy? Well, judging on this video, it may help ESRI's ArcMap users improve their efficiency in some cases. From the developer in a SA's comment: "This is my own temporary solution until ESRI or 3Dconnxion releases the &amp;#8220;official&amp;#8221; driver. I just love SpaceNavigator, and I couldn&amp;#8217;t wait. I tested this &amp;#8220;beta&amp;#8221; driver using ArcMap 9.1 and 9.2, and it seems to work."</description>

<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-29T13:28:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>virtualglobe</dc:subject>
<slash:department>will-it-be-your-next-mouse?</slash:department>
<slash:section>technology</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/218214&amp;from=rss">
<title>Inrix Predictive and Real-Time Traffic Service from Multiple Sources</title>

<link>http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/218214&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>All Points Blog discuss a new service by Inrix which provide predictive and real-time traffic service for Windows Mobile devices. This site indicates which information is used: "Inrix acquires real-time and historical sensor data from hundreds of public and private sources including anonymous, real-time GPS probe data from more than 625,000 commercial fleet, delivery and taxi vehicles; toll tag data; and occupancy and speed measurements from Department of Transportation sensor networks. Additionally, the Inrix Smart Dust Network aggregates real-time incidents and hundreds of market-specific criteria that affect traffic &amp;#8211; such as construction and road closures, sporting and entertainment events, school schedules and weather forecasts." See the numerous related stories below.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-28T21:58:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>transportation</dc:subject>
<slash:department>but-you-can't-never-show-up-to-the-office</slash:department>
<slash:section>application_domains</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>

</item>

<item rdf:about="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/2055253&amp;from=rss">
<title>Geolocated Classified Ads</title>
<link>http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/2055253&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The Google Earth Blog introduces the Safarii website for geolocated classified ads. Here's the Safarii's Google Earth page. From the entry: ""...it gathers classifieds listings from Google Base, Oodle (and soon Vast), matches them against any set of filters you specify, and then overlays them on Google Earth as you are flying around!" You can set up a filter to look only at the information you want. For example, you can look just for "Vehicles" and filter for "Lexus" and between a certain price range."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-28T20:56:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>marketing</dc:subject>
<slash:department>know-where-you-buy</slash:department>

<slash:section>application_domains</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/1424242&amp;from=rss">
<title>Mapping Worldwide Libraries Information</title>
<link>http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/1424242&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The Map Room links to a tool to map worldwide library statistics. From their about page: "WorldMap allows users to select a data set, then represents the data geographically by country on a world map. (For many data sets, data also may be displayed for U.S. states and Canadian provinces.) The collection data for the map were generated from WorldCat, and gathered from more than thirty other sources."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-28T14:20:00+00:00</dc:date>

<dc:subject>maps</dc:subject>
<slash:department>Alexandria-everywhere</slash:department>
<slash:section>application_domains</slash:section>
<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>1,1,1,1,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/1417231&amp;from=rss">
<title>Mapping Space Routes</title>
<link>http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/28/1417231&amp;from=rss</link>

<description>Very Spatial links to an article regarding a MIT project doing route analysis in space. From the article: "The system is based on a network of nodes on planetary surfaces, in stable orbits around the Earth, the moon or Mars, or at well-defined points in space where the gravitational force between the two bodies (in this case, the Earth and the moon) cancel each other out. [...] They also experimented with modern logistics technologies, such as radio frequency identification, that autonomously manage and track assets with the goal of creating a "smart exploration base" that could increase safety and save astronauts and explorers precious time."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-28T14:18:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>space_exploration</dc:subject>
<slash:department>I-wanna-be-test-driver</slash:department>
<slash:section>application_domains</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/2023250&amp;from=rss">

<title>New Map Resource- Useamap.com</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/2023250&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>Vincent Glennon writes "I have a free site which your readers might indeed find useful at http://useamap.com./ It which allows you to save a location for an event with a short URL. For example, if you are meeting a couple of friends, who are flying into the city for the first time, you can save your meeting location with a link like useamap.com/meet_here on a map. Then you can tell them over the phone where to meet up exactly, instead of making your own map or giving them your own directions. It is very easy to put (embed) the map onto your blog and anyone going to your location can get detailed driving directions to your location. The site is currently being used quite a lot by opencoffee meetings which is an informal event linking budding entrepreneurs and investors together as well as IT related folk. One example is the Paris opencoffee event which is being held at http://useamap.com/opencoffeeparis. Let me know if you have any questions. Best Regards, Vincent Glennon" Here's the feature list. It offers some added value over a simple and direct Google Maps URL.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-27T20:36:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>webmapping</dc:subject>
<slash:department>maps-in-the-hands-of-everyone</slash:department>
<slash:section>technology</slash:section>

<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/148259&amp;from=rss">
<title>MapDotNet Server 2007 Launches</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/148259&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The LM/VE blog links (with screenshots) to the MapDotNet Server 2007 software which just became available. Here's what it is from the website: "With MapDotNet Server 2007 developers can build .NET web mapping applications without the overhead costs of other server based GIS products. MapDotNet Server 2007 uses a custom, built-in rendering engine for your web application's maps. Drag and drop server controls allow you to connect to spatial data stores like ArcSDE&amp;#174; or PostGIS. MapDotNet Server can also be a tile server for Microsoft's Virtual Earth."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-27T14:54:00+00:00</dc:date>

<dc:subject>webmapping</dc:subject>
<slash:department>in-the-flood-of-webmapping-software</slash:department>
<slash:section>technology</slash:section>
<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>1,1,1,1,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/1354248&amp;from=rss">
<title>Topology -&gt; Geography</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/27/1354248&amp;from=rss</link>

<description>Anonymous Voxel writes "There are established tools that analyse geographic objects and extract the topological relationships, what polygon borders what polygon, etc. Is there anything that does the reverse? That is a tool that given a set of topological relationships, can build a simple geography that matches it? For example; I would describe the topological relationships as something like this;region A connects to regions B, C &amp;amp; Dregion B connects to regions A &amp;amp; Eregion C connects to region Aand so on. And then the (hypothetical) tool would construct geometry that satisfies the above topological relationships, whilst also being reasonably pleasing to the eye. In this case five polygons or boxes, either bordering each other, or maybe connected by lines."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-27T13:58:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>ask_slashgeo</dc:subject>
<slash:department>bring-topology-to-your-geography</slash:department>
<slash:section>technology</slash:section>
<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>3,3,3,3,2,1,0</slash:hit_parade>

</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1624220&amp;from=rss">
<title>Massive Street-level Camera Acquisition on the Way?</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1624220&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>All Points Blog links to an article about camera data acquisition and their potential integration to virtual globe apps. From the article: "IMC has started an initiative to capture complete street-level views of 25 major U.S. cities. McGovern notes that they drive specially outfitted Volkswagens up and down all the streets, then fill in the gaps, like New York's Central Park, with backpack-mounted units. [...] "If they have New York City or Chicago captured, then it makes sense to make it available through Google Earth. That allows you to distribute it easily, and Google has hundreds of millions of users that you can spread the cost over."" See also related stories below.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-26T17:18:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>satellites_sensors</dc:subject>
<slash:department>welcome-to-your-virtual-city</slash:department>

<slash:section>technology</slash:section>
<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>1,1,1,1,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1424258&amp;from=rss">
<title>National Mapping VS Public Domain Mapping</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1424258&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>Vector One offers an interesting reflexion on the debate between national mapping efforts and public-driven mapping such as OpenStreetMap. From the entry: "As can be seen, there is a wide difference between origins of national mapping agencies and their current operations. The word &amp;#8216;mapping&amp;#8217; in their titles may confuse matters more than help, particularly to those who equate all spatial or a sense of &amp;#8216;geospatial&amp;#8217; to the web map alone. These organisations are not solely map agencies. Their tasks and operations vary."</description>

<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-26T16:17:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>data_sharing</dc:subject>
<slash:department>what-is-best-for-you?</slash:department>
<slash:section>technology</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1417202&amp;from=rss">
<title>Dangermond on GIS as a New Medium and the GeoWeb</title>

<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1417202&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The Geography Matters blog summarizes an article by Jack Dangermond, ESRI's president, on GIS as a new medium and the GeoWeb. From the article: "GIS is being used to model the physical and cultural knowledge of our world, breaking it down into components and subsystems, providing us with systematic knowledge, an integrative framework, analytic methods, and intuitive visualization. GIS is attractive to humans because it responds to both the cognitive as well as intuitive dimensions of understanding. GIS creates order and meaning. It is helping us define interconnections and interdependencies, and it provides a broad understanding of nature and human ecology."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-26T15:09:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>esri</dc:subject>
<georss:point>34.0575 -117.1955</georss:point>
<slash:department>how-does-stakeholders-see-the-future-</slash:department>
<slash:section>industry</slash:section>

<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1323228&amp;from=rss">
<title>New Open Source Utility Library for the Google Maps API</title>
<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1323228&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The Geowanking mailing list tells us Google has opened parts of the Google Maps API for open source development. From the announcement: "Another reason for this open source project is that we've realized that there are many potential extensions for the Google Maps API, but that the common user still needs a reliable and quick-loading API. Adding custom controls/functionality to the core API adds to the file size and forces developers wanting to tweak the code to overwrite obfuscated JS functions. With this open source project, a developer can include the JavaScript file for the particular library they're interested in. They can even download a copy of it and tweak it for their use."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-26T14:07:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>google</dc:subject>

<georss:point>37.389 -122.0385</georss:point>
<slash:department>between-do-not-eveil-and-commercial-offers</slash:department>
<slash:section>industry</slash:section>
<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>2,2,2,2,2,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1316219&amp;from=rss">
<title>Washington State To Try RFID Drivers Licenses</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/26/1316219&amp;from=rss</link>

<description>Slashdot discuss the introduction of RFID in drivers licenses in the Washington State. Their summary: "[...] a program the state of Washington has approved, to issue RFID-equipped drivers licenses to facilitate cross-border traffic. The idea is to load the drivers license with information proving citizenship, so that (with Department of Homeland Security approval) the bearer doesn't need to carry a passport &amp;#8212; which otherwise will be required to re-enter the US from Canada beginning in 2009. The "enhanced" licenses will require applicants to submit to an in-person interview and to show proof of citizenship. A pilot program in Washington begins January 2008. Officials hope for DHS approval of the program before the Vancouver Olympics in 2010 causes a spike in cross-border traffic."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-26T13:22:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>rfid</dc:subject>
<georss:point>47.260592 -121.442871</georss:point>
<slash:department>will-they-ever-learn-about-RFID-and-security</slash:department>
<slash:section>technology</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>

</item>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/1435228&amp;from=rss">
<title>The GeoClue Project: Geographic Information Service for Apps</title>
<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/1435228&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The High Earth Orbit blog links to the GeoGlue project which aims at providing a geographic information service for applications. This project in development will be presented at the GNOME conference in Birmingham, UK. From the website: "GeoClue is a project that provide all kinds of geography information to an application. This is through a very abstract DBus interface in which a variety of backends can be used to provide this implementation. Although we implement a few reference backends, creating your own is encouraged. There are many separate APIs that are planned including * Position * Map * Routing * Geocode * Track Logs" From the presentation's synopsis: "Emerging open-standards such as GeoRSS, KML, geo-uri, and Geo W3C all enable easy publishing and sharing of geographic information from many data sources. GeoClue aims to provide users with a application that can determine their position from a variety of location providers and find information that is local to them."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-23T16:14:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>opensource_community</dc:subject>
<georss:point>33.517354 -86.802464</georss:point>

<slash:department>projects-that-sticks-to-geospatial</slash:department>
<slash:section>industry</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/1423244&amp;from=rss">
<title>The Architecture of the GeoWeb</title>
<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/1423244&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The import cartography blog adds precision to an entry on the architecture of the GeoWeb, preceding the GeoWeb conference to be held in July. From the entry: "For a GeoWeb to work, we need to extend the Search Engine's index to incorporate some type of spatial index such as an R-Tree, Quad-Tree or some combination. This enables objects to be indexed by their location (where on the earth's surface) rather than just by some keyword. Note that this can proceed in a couple of different directions. Document items may contain references to places (e.g. place names) which can then be located and spatially indexed. Other information may be inherently spatial in nature such as a GIS data set, an ESRI Shape or GML File etc. These can also be spatially indexed by an appropriate Spatial Robot [...]"</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>

<dc:date>2007-03-23T15:15:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>research</dc:subject>
<georss:point>49.282168 -123.125968</georss:point>
<slash:department>this-building-should-stand-high-and-strait</slash:department>
<slash:section>industry</slash:section>
<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>1,1,1,1,1,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/146219&amp;from=rss">

<title>ESRI Developer Summit Day 2</title>
<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/23/146219&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>A followup to yesterday's summary of ESRI Developer Summit, geospatial blogs run a new salve of entries: Dot Not Without a Net shares thoughts and session summaries, Steve's Little world is inspired by GeoDatabase replication and turbocharging and discuss the Web Service API to ArcGIS Server and .NET and Java. Dave Bouwman shares the presentation file about this .NET SIG presentation. The Memory Leak discuss ArcGIS geoprocessing.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-23T14:08:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>esri</dc:subject>
<georss:point>33.829072 -116.540909</georss:point>
<slash:department>learning-by-listening</slash:department>

<slash:section>industry</slash:section>
<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>1,1,1,1,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/2119234&amp;from=rss">
<title>KML and GeoRSS Support in the Google Maps API Announced</title>
<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/2119234&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The import cartography blog links to the announcement of Google Maps API's support for GeoRSS feed and KML mapping. Surprisingly, the official blog takes Slashgeo's GeoRSS feed as example (thanks Nigel)! Too bad we haven't completed the work on our GeoRSS Feed (example: non-main page geolocated stories are not yet included in our GeoRSS feed). From the announcement: "To start we now support GeoRSS as a data format for geographic content in Google Maps. We want to enable users to create data in whatever format is most convenient for them, and feel that by supporting both KML and GeoRSS we can enable a wider variety of people and applications to contribute content to Google Maps. We've built support for the Simple, GML, and W3C Geo encodings of GeoRSS -- all you have to do is enter the full URL of a GeoRSS file into the Maps query box to load the file." Obviously, the official GeoRSS blog covers the story. Links to other GeoRSS-related stories below.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>

<dc:date>2007-03-22T21:19:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>google</dc:subject>
<georss:point>37.389 -122.0385</georss:point>
<slash:department>supporting-emerging-standards</slash:department>
<slash:section>industry</slash:section>
<slash:comments>11</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>11,11,11,11,8,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/143250&amp;from=rss">

<title>Mapping the Index of Economic Freedom</title>
<link>http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/143250&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The Catholicgauze blog has a nice analysis of the Index of Economic Freedom map. The Index is published by The Heritage Foundation. From the blog: "The top seven all have been strongly culturally influenced by England and the English ideals of personal and economic freedoms. [...] A secondary break down has Hong Kong and Singapore as Asian tigers. [...] The bottom fifteen countries include Venezuela, Iran, Zimbabwe, Libya, Cuba, and North Korea. The bottom part of the list coincides with Thomas Barnett's Gap. These countries are either African, Islamic, Communist/Thug Communist, or a combination of the variables."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-22T14:55:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>globalization</dc:subject>
<georss:point>0 0</georss:point>
<slash:department>free-as-in-speech</slash:department>

<slash:section>application_domains</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/149239&amp;from=rss">
<title>OpenStreetMap Subsidised in the Netherlands</title>
<link>http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/149239&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The OpenStreetMap project received money for mapping in the Netherlands. From the blog: "he Dutch branch of OpenStreetMap received a grant of 12.000 euro! The goal is to organise ten mapping parties in the coming nine months. Focus will be on mapping Amsterdam, Rotterdam and the Hague and - most importantly - to get the community jump started in the Netherlands."</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-22T14:15:00+00:00</dc:date>

<dc:subject>maps</dc:subject>
<georss:point>52.372246 4.892864</georss:point>
<slash:department>money-for-public-initiatives</slash:department>
<slash:section>application_domains</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/1344213&amp;from=rss">
<title>ESRI Developer Summit News Summary</title>
<link>http://industry.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/22/1344213&amp;from=rss</link>

<description>This week's annual ESRI developer summit makes digital ink flow on the numerous geospatial blogs. Here's a few of them discussing their first day: The Memory Leak, Spatially Adjusted, Steve's Little world blog entries, scrappad blog, Dave Bouwman's blog and Directions Mag lists the numerous podcasts related to the event. Anyone striving to get all the ESRI Developer Summit news as fast as possible, read PlanetGS.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-22T13:46:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>esri</dc:subject>
<georss:point>33.829072 -116.540909</georss:point>
<slash:department>welcome-to-the-ESRI-church</slash:department>
<slash:section>industry</slash:section>
<slash:hit_parade>0,0,0,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/2050218&amp;from=rss">
<title>Thinking about Studying GIS / Geomatics</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/2050218&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>bloc writes "I hope I'm posting this in the right place. I'm thinking about getting either a BSi in Geography with a diploma in GIS (at my preferred university) or a degree in Geomatics. How are the two different? Would you strongly recommend one over the other? I get the impression that a lot of people with Geography degrees end up teaching, am I right in thinking that? Also, I'm not a strong math person, will this really hold me back? Thanks for the help" See related stories.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-21T21:05:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>ask_slashgeo</dc:subject>
<slash:department>take-the-dive-into-a-great-future</slash:department>

<slash:section>technology</slash:section>
<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>3,3,3,3,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/1717216&amp;from=rss">
<title>NASA's Global Map Projector</title>
<link>http://technology.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/1717216&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>The Map Room links to the free NASA Global Map Projector software. From the website: "G.Projector is a Java application which allows you to explore a large collection of global map projections and project an input GIF, JPG or PNG equirectangular map image. Lon-lat gridlines and continental outlines may be drawn, and resulting map images may be saved to disk in GIF, PDF, PNG or PS form." The Map Room also links to an exhaustive gallery of map projections. See related stories below for an online java projection tool.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>

<dc:date>2007-03-21T17:10:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>geocoding</dc:subject>
<slash:department>project-yourself-on-the-map</slash:department>
<slash:section>technology</slash:section>
<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
<slash:hit_parade>1,1,1,0,0,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<item rdf:about="http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/1311251&amp;from=rss">
<title>Residential Wi-Fi Mapping Database Revealed</title>

<link>http://appdomains.slashgeo.org/article.pl?sid=07/03/21/1311251&amp;from=rss</link>
<description>Slashdot discuss a story about a residential WiFi hotspots mapping database. Their summary: "An enormous database of home wifi routers and their locations has been revealed after the Internet Patrol did some digging following AOL's recent announcement of their new "Near Me" service, which allows AIM users to see which of their instant messenger buddies are geographically near them. The database, containing the unique IDs of more than 16 million wireless routers and their locations, has been compiled by AOL partner Skyhook Wireless, which claims to have mapped the majority of residences in the U.S. and Canada." All Points Blog provides additional context. The AnyGeo blog add information about the Spotigo hotspots and TeleAtlas' ContentLink program.</description>
<dc:creator>Satri</dc:creator>
<dc:date>2007-03-21T14:07:00+00:00</dc:date>
<dc:subject>maps</dc:subject>
<slash:department>wifi-is-in-the-air</slash:department>
<slash:section>application_domains</slash:section>
<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>

<slash:hit_parade>2,2,2,1,1,0,0</slash:hit_parade>
</item>

<textinput rdf:about="http://slashgeo.org/search.pl">
<title>Search Slashgeo</title>
<description>Search Slashgeo stories</description>
<name>query</name>
<link>http://slashgeo.org/search.pl</link>
</textinput>

</rdf:RDF>